# Emmanuel Oladimeji Adeyemi



yemicodes@gmail.com



+2349026863277



linkedin.com/in/emmanuel-adeyemi-3733b8208



https://www.9trocoder.com

## **Summary**

PWA EXPERT.

Passionate software engineer with 2-3 years of industry experience in full-stack development, front-end development, and user experience in Agile. I obtained REACT.js Certifications from UDEMY. I am looking to deliver excellent Web Development Skills to help grow business and Innovative ideas.

Professional Skills
Analytical thinking
Resolving technical issues
Communication skills
Teamwork
Adaptability

Top Skills

Git

GitHub

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

JavaScripit

Nodejs

Npm

**PWA** 

React.js

NEXT.js

Vercel

Firebase

MongoDB

**Express** 

MERN

UI/UX

tailwindcss

Languages

English: Fluent

Turkish: Intermediate

GitHub: https://github.com/9trocoder?tab=repositories

Email: yemicodes@gmail.com

### **Experience**

Senior Developer

Glitz Blockonomics Feb 2022 - Jun 2022 (5 months)

■ Web Developer

SwayStock Jan 2022 - Aug 2022 (8 months)

Rrontend Web Developer

**GEFEASOFT** 

May 2021 - Jun 2021 (2 months)

Web Developer

Githarita

Dec 2020 - Mar 2021 (4 months)

Frontend Developer

Oversabi

Sep 2020 - Mar 2021 (7 months)

#### **Education**

Cyprus International University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Sep 2018 - Sep 2022

# (A) freeCodeCamp

Full Stack Web Development Certification, Computer Science Sep 2017 - May 2018

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Microservices with Node JS and React - Udemy UC-70c840aa-d142-46d6-83b6-e6475d3ba0ae

Node.js, Express, MongoDB: The Complete Bootcamp 2022 - Udemy: Online Courses

UC-d44cef1c-2e3b-470d-8143-2508d8bd9fb3

**Microfrontends with React: A Complete Developer's Guide** - Udemy: Online Courses

UC-10bf1245-48f1-46e4-97bd-132505504b3e

React - The Complete Guide (Hooks, React Router, Redux) - Udemy: Online Courses

UC-e2956d9a-a5e9-4d95-a5ad-39c1109055ae

- Complete React Developer (Redux, Hooks, GraphQL) Udemy: Online Courses UC-aff2a8b4-93e3-4bdf-b5b0-483493f51130
- The complete React 18 Fullstack course (2022 edition) Udemy: Online Courses UC-141d5f4c-9d35-4f68-9f08-60b96a5cd7c0
- information Architecture (IA) Fundamental Udemy UC-b1abd873-947e-4b90-82b1-cc854549536c
- **UX Design & User Experience Design Course** Udemy UC-9XVLC7F1

#### **Skills**

MERN Stack • HTML • Progressive Web Applications (PWAs) • Flutter • JavaScript • Firebase • Express.js • React.js • Next.js • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)